saferpay.com 2007-12-17

# Saferpay - Privacy Policy

This document was last updated January 1, 2003.

At Telekurs Card Solutions (saferpay.com), we are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself, but we do sometimes need information to provide the services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read the complete saferpay.com privacy statement.

## Collecting your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to register before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, or when purchasing and registering saferpay products. Personal information collected by saferpay.com is often limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information if this is needed to.

For example, if you choose to make a purchase in the Shop area of the Web site, we will request personal information such as: name, address, telephone number, credit card number and shipping information.

When you buy and install saferpay products, we will create a personal profile for you. We keep this information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site. This is considered your personal profile.

If you ever want to review or update your profile, you will find most of the information in your personal website, such as mysaferpay.

## Use of your Personal Information

We use your personal information for four primary purposes:  

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.
  * To allow you access to the purchased services on saferpay.com.
  * To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Microsoft.

saferpay.com will not disclose your personal information to anybody else.

## Control of your Personal Information

When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, saferpay.com will not share that information with third parties without your permission. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

saferpay.com may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service issues related to a product or service you requested. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen.

## Access to your Personal Information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. If you want to review and update this information, you can call us at any time at the Call Center.

## Security of your Personal Information

saferpay.com strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in Switzerland or any other country where saferpay or its subsidiaries are located.

## Use of Cookies

We use cookies during the payment process to store your payment context while processing the transaction and to check your login state. We do not track individuals' use of the site.

When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously.

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the saferpay.com Web site, you will not be able to execute transactions through saferpay.com.

## Changes to this Statement

saferpay.com will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the «last updated» date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, saferpay.com will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.

## Contact Information

saferpay welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us by e-mail, or postal mail. 

Telekurs Card Solutions Ltd.   
Hardturmstrasse 201   
P.O. Box   
CH - 8021 Zürich 

Tel: +41 (0)848 66 44 44   
Fax: +41 (0)848 66 44 45  
E-mail: info@saferpay.com
